Why didn't you ask me? I know a million theater jokes.
What's the deal with those guys down in the pit?
-They're musicians. That's not a joke.
-It's a funny observation.
Severance package.
The Yankees are giving me three months full pay for doing nothing.
They did it for three years. What's another few months.
I'm really going to do something with these three months.
Like what?
I'm gonna read a book. From beginning to end.
In that order.
I've always wanted to do that
I'm gonna play frolf.
You mean golf?
Frolf, frisbee golf Jerry.
Golf with a frisbee.
Time to taste the fruits and let the juices drip down my chin.
I proclaim this: The Summer of George!